Everyone...
Why?
Because we're worried about you.
I'm fine.
That's why...
You don't have to worry.
Get away...
Oh, that's great!
Just what we want from
the great One For All successor!
So...
Are you able to smile right now?!
In order to smile...
For everyone to live in peace...
I have to go...
That's why...
Get out of the way, everyone!
Make us, you All Might wannabe!
Midoriya, I know that you haven't changed.
Let's do this, everyone!
Yeah!
In a world where there's no black or white
I cried in the depths of hatred
Not even allowed to stop,
we just have to move
Forward beyond that
I impatiently acted rashly on my own
The fate that I'd carried until now
You have a hard time even walking
Is there still a way to save you?
When you feel like you're about to give up
I'll rush to wherever you are
We won't let go of any of
our feelings either, any of them
Even if you say it's none of my business,
I still want to be by your side
That's what it means to be a hero
I won't lose any of the voices
that came together either, any of them
I'll get up again as
many times as it takes
Let's go and put our lives on the line
My soul cries out in
response to your feelings
I won't hesitate anymore, so let's go
To the ends of true worth
"Tenya Iida - Quirk: Engine"
Stop it!
Run away!
I told you, didn't I?
It has nothing to do with you!
If you say that,
then heroes can't do anything!
It's like what All Might said:
Meddling when you don't need to...
...is the essence of being a hero.
That's right.
I know very well that you can't be
stopped once you've decided something.
We heard! That you unlocked
the Fourth's and Sixth's Quirks!
"Izuku Midoriya - Quirk: One For All"
Your look's totally different now!
"Katsuki Bakugo - Quirk: Explosion"
Damn nerd!
Thanks... for coming...
Sixth!
This is...
Smokescreen!
"Ochaco Uraraka - Quirk: Zero Gravity"
In the documents we got,
that's the Sixth's...
Guys, make sure he doesn't get away!
Land Mine Blast!
Trying to run away without even talking?!
Now that you can
do anything and everything,
those around you end up
looking like extras, huh?!
They said it's okay for you to come back!
Midoriya! The principal said
that you're welcome to come back!
"Koji Koda - Quirk: Anivoice"
Okay? So don't run away!
Koda...
Sorry.
Letting that hang out
all the time's scary!
"Hanta Sero - Quirk: Tape"
No wonder people are wary of you!
Just aim for the strike zone.
Think of it as an extension of your body.
I see.
Wow! That really does make a difference!
Sero...
Heartbeat Wall!
He's fast!
Midoriya!
This isn't that important,
but during the school festival, when you
helped me summarize points in my notes,
you totally saved me!
Advice for the band members?!
Wow!
This makes me happy!
I kind of got over enthusiastic
and wrote too much.
It was just a small thing,
"Kyoka Jiro - Quirk: Earphone Jack"
but I was really happy!
Twirling Tail Dance!
"Mashirao Ojiro - Quirk: Tail"
Do you remember the match against
Shinso during the sports festival?
I'm going to say something selfish,
but please do your best for me, too.
I'll never forget how
you got mad for my sake!
I can't let you be the only one
to fight all beat up like that!
If I'm there...
...you're all in danger...
You'll be taken by All For One...!
That's why...
...I left!
Push, Dark Shadow!
That guy's gotten too strong!
And stubborn!
"Rikido Sato - Quirk: Sugar Rush"
Midoriya!
Listen!
You might have some special powers,
but your feelings are the same as ours!
What Koda said about
the school earlier, too!
Hear us out!
If you don't, then I won't let
you use any of my food coloring
when you make
candy apples for Eri anymore!
That's fine.
Eri doesn't need them... from me...
At first, we were all
planning on going with you.
But right now, with Endeavor
and the others' cooperation,
we're using our Quirks.
"Momo Yaoyorozu - Quirk: Creation"
With the mission of securing your safety.
A device to put me to sleep, huh?
You don't...
...have to bother with me anymore!
Get away from me!
No way!
Midoriya!
"Denki Kaminari - Quirk: Electrification"
I know One For All's
important and everything,
but right now, you've got
something even more important!
Our hobbies are totally different,
but you're my friend!
That's why I'll do this
even if it's against your will!
I said...
I've wrapped them in electrical tape--
made by Yaoyorozu!
"Mezo Shoji - Quirk: Dupli-Arms"
What you said when
we were attacked at camp...
Honestly, with this group...
...we could probably
even go up against All Might.
That's what you said!
This place is nice and dark.
"Fumikage Tokoyami - Quirk: Dark Shadow"
Dark Shadow!
Ragnarok: Womb!
To use Dark Shadow's
offensive ability defensively--
That was your idea.
--Midoriya!
Are we just objects to protect to you?!
Just take a bath, okay?!
Midoriya, let's go take a bath!
Please...
Midoriya!
I can't believe he broke out of Ragnarok!
That's...
The power of One For All...!
Please, stop!
I know...
I know you're worried about me.
I know you're worried
from the bottom of your hearts.
I know.
Because Danger Sense, which is
supposed to alert me to danger or evil,
hasn't been activating at all.
That's why...
I want you to get away... please...
I'm... fine!
Heaven-Piercing Ice Wall!
What's with that face?
Does your responsibility...
not allow you to cry?
"Shoto Todoroki - Quirk: Half-Cold Half-Hot"
That responsibility...
Let us share it with you.
Midoriya!
I won't let you go.
I thought I'd stopped you, so I was filled
with disappointment and bad feelings...
I didn't know what to say...
I'm not going to cry like I did back then.
You're dear to me...
...so when it's scary,
I'll tremble with you,
and when it's painful, I'll cry with you.
You're my friend...
If you're going to be
like a comic book hero,
we won't let you go alone!
"Tsuyu Asui - Quirk: Frog"
"Deku vs. Class A"
Endeavor!
Bakugo, Todoroki, and Yaoyorozu
worked together to capture him.
"Pro Hero - Endeavor - Quirk: Hellflame"
I just chipped him out of the ice.
Dictator... He's not
necessarily working alone.
Right now, we need to make sure
those anti-hero civilians are safe, too.
Go help secure this area
like Hawks and the others.
Endeavor.
Should we get Jeanist
to settle this quickly after all...?
Oh, damn it, if he's moving around
that much, I won't be able to do much.
"Eijiro Kirishima - Quirk: Hardening"
There's a ton I want to say to him, too!
Me, too!
Oui!
Endeavor?
Hawks, don't let anyone
bother them right now...
Midoriya!
This situation might be
just what All For One is after!
He might go after U.A.
while we're occupied here!
If you haven't been able to find them
even after running around that much,
then you need a plan B!
If you want to protect U.A.,
then you could also choose
to stay by it and not leave!
Let us fight with you!
I can't...
Next, it's...
...your turn.
Midoriya!
I can't...
Next, it's...
...your turn.
Because this is a fight between
One For All and All For One...
You guys... can't keep up!
Uraraka!
Midoriya!
Mineta Beads: Tenfold!
"Minoru Mineta - Quirk: Pop Off"
I've never thought your power
was cool or anything!
What made me fall for you
was when you were sweating bullets,
trembling with fear,
when we opened up a path together!
How you were back then!
Sorry... Mineta!
Midoriya!
Blackwhip's elasticity plus
One For All 45% plus Fa Jin!
Faux 100--
I won't let you go!
Deku!
It's different from back then!
I think Bakugo will feel humiliated
that he had to be saved by everyone...
I...
Everyone!
Protective Coating Style
at 0.1% acidity! Acidman!
"Mina Ashido - Quirk: Acid"
Go, Todoroki!
Push them out, Dark Shadow!
Flashfreeze Heatwave!
There's so much I want to say...
We can't keep up?!
Deku, we...
...don't want to be protected,
and we don't want to reject you.
Explosive Speed Turbo...
Cluster!
--Go...!
Go!
We just want to be by your side.
Deku, there's still stuff
I want--no, I need to say to you!
But for now,
I'll wait until after this guy,
with his body built for speed!
Prez!
Midoriya, you're always going ahead of me.
That's why... That's why...
I'll always...
...be ready...
...to challenge you!
If there were one thing Izuku Midoriya
needs right now, it would be...
...those who will, with the
same intent, at the same pace--
continue to run alongside him.
No... Let go... of me!
I won't let go!
I'll come running no matter where to take
the hand of a lost child! I'm Ingenium!
Meddling when you don't need to...
...is the essence of being a hero, right?
"Tenya Iida"
"Katsuki Bakugo"
I have to shake him off...
But I have no strength left...
Uraraka!
Release!
Can I land safely...?
Okay, okay!
Kirishima!
"Toru Hagakure - Quirk: Invisibility"
"Yuga Aoyama - Quirk: Navel Laser"
Are you okay?!
You can't... get me down!
Midoriya!
In the past! I was so moved
by this thing that happened!
When a kid the same age as me
rushed out in order to save his friend!
That was you, wasn't it?!
It doesn't matter if it's
a special power or whatever!
I think the you back then
is the answer for us now!
Midoriya!
I don't want anyone else to go away!
Let's stick together!
Let's go to class again with everyone!
Midoriya...
Hey...
I... wish I could...
But...
...I'm scared.
There are a lot of people at U.A.
I don't want to cause them any trouble.
Things can't go back
to the way they were before...
When Shigaraki stabbed me,
do you remember what I said?
No, I don't.
I said, "Don't try to win by yourself."
There was more to that.
My body moved on its own,
and then I got stabbed.
I thought I should tell you.
I looked down on you our whole lives...
because you were Quirkless.
You were obviously way behind me,
but I felt like you were
way ahead of me, too.
I didn't like it.
I didn't want to see you.
I didn't want to accept you.
That's why I bullied you
to get away from you.
I tried to feel superior by rejecting you.
I was always losing to you.
After getting into U.A., not a
single thing went the way I wanted.
Every day, I was made to feel how
strong you were and how weak I was.
It's not something that'll work
itself out just by saying it out loud,
but it's how I really feel, Izuku.
I'm sorry for everything.
Everything you've done after
inheriting One For All has been ideal.
You've done nothing wrong.
But right now, you're unsteady.
There's a wall you can't
overcome with just ideals.
We'll take care of the things
that you can't take care of.
In order to surpass the ideal,
we need to save you,
the refugees at U.A.,
and all the people in the city.
You've all already...
far surpassed... me...
I'm sorry for saying...
that you couldn't keep up...
I know.
It looks like we've cleared
the first hurdle, at least.
It'll be even tougher from here on out.
Oh, his eyes are open!
Thirteen, he's awake.
Oh, good.
Can you hear me, Midoriya?
Yes...
Right now, most of the civilians have been
evacuated to shelters across the country.
The ones left outside
are anti-hero vigilante groups
and rioting extremists taking advantage
of what the jailbreakers started.
"Pro Hero - Thirteen - Quirk: Black Hole"
Members of the anti-hero groups
have also become exhausted
and more are entering the shelters.
Because most of the
rioters have formed gangs,
they're easy to get rid of.
As the evacuation continues,
we've had to split our forces
to deal with everything.
Everyone's doing their
best to improve the situation.
The help you'd been providing outside
is able to be taken care of
by other heroes or the police.
U-U... A...?
The U.A. Barrier is up and running!
And this wall is just
the tip of the iceberg!
You'll be totally surprised
once you hear about the system!
They said we can combine with Shiketsu!
I want to respond to everyone
in Class A's feelings...
But...
I can't... go back...
It's noisy inside.
Prioritize our safety!
Our safety!
Don't let that boy into U.A.!
Don't let him in!
He's the boy that Shigaraki
is rumored to be after, isn't he?!
Hey, hey, calm down!
Hey, didn't you hear
the principal's explanation?
He said they'd guarantee our safety!
So guarantee it!
We can't accept this!
We can't!
--Hey--
--We were told that it'd be safe!
That's why we came!
Why would you put a bomb in here?!
Yeah!
You could put him
somewhere that's not U.A.!
If you're gonna hide him,
do it somewhere else!
Somewhere else!
It's all right.
Iida and the others started
spinning this together,
and then Bakugo added his thread...
All of us--
We will not let you go. We can't.
When heroes suffering,
who will protect the heroes?
"Preview"
Here's the preview.
I want to tell the past me--
You're not special.
You're just walking one step at
a time down the path you believe in.
There are people looking
at those footprints.
Next time, "A Young Woman's Declaration."
Leave behind a path, Izuku Midoriya!
Go beyond!
"Next time: A Young Woman's Declaration"
Plus Ultra!